ALBERT JOAN AGRAMONTE SUERO

Dominican Republic \diamond (809) · 854 · 1810 albertjohan2707@gmail.com

SOCIAL LINKS

Links GitHub, LinkedIn, Portfolio

PROFILE

I'm passionate about programming. As a software developer, I like to innovate and work as a team. In my experience, colleagues are the most important in the working environment.

I have worked on certain personal and professional projects, which have allowed me to gain experience dealing with code and other people.

I plan to give everything for the company that is working and thus give to demonstrate my full potential to get to know me and continue growing as a developer.

EDUCATION

Brigham Young school

Aug 2016

Bachelor

Here I took my bachelor's degree, where I obtained the basic knowledge of the English language.

Institute of Technology of the Americas(Itla)

Aug 2020

Technologist

Here I spent my entire career as a software developer.

Technological Institute of Santo Domingo(Intec)

Nov 2023

Engineering

Currently, I'm pursuing my career as a software engineer here.

EXPERIENCE

Camsoft

Jun 2023 - Present

junior Programmer

Santo Domingo

· In camsoft, I am as a junior programmer where I develop as fullstack. In it, I have to give everything for the whole, both backend and frontend.

Simetrica Consulting

Apr 2023 - Jun 2023

junior Programmer

Santo Domingo

· In this company I did my internship, in which I stood out as a backend developer, working in the c# and programming language. net framework. Where I made apis with my colleagues.

COURSES

 JavaScript - Udemy
 Jul 2022-Aug 2022

 Node.js - Udemy
 Aug 2022-Sept 2022

 Express.js - Udemy
 Oct 2022 - Dic 2022

 TailwindCss - Udemy
 Dic 2022-Jan 2022

TypeScript Apr 2024

TECHNICAL STRENGTHS

Computer Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, C#, Python TailwindCSS, Sequelize, Express.js, .NET

Libraries:React, AxiosProtocols & APIs:JSON, RESTDatabases:MySQL, SQL Server

Tools: Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, Postman, Jira, Docker

Others: Git, GitHub, GitLab, Node.js, HTML, CSS, Sass

CERTIFICATIONS

Scrum Foundation Professional Certification - SFPC

Mar 2023 CertiProf

Scrum Foundation Professional Certification holders have developed entry-level skills in Scrum that endorse their fundamental knowledge in this framework.

Mastering TypeScript - 2024 Edition

Apr 2024 Udemy

Credential

Legacy JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

Aug 2023 fre

freeCodeCamp

Credential

REFERENCES

Edwin Roman	Software Developer	(829) 418-9788
Alam Emil Soto Del Jesus	Software Developer	(829) 397-5412